<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">MyCollection</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add">Add</string>
    <string name="title_activity_login">Login</string>
    <string name="title_activity_counter">Counter</string>
    <string name="title_activity_geek">Geek</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">Main</string>
    <string name="fnumber">first Number</string>
    <string name="snumber">second Number</string>
    <string name="result">Result:</string>
    <string name="btnAdd">Add</string>
    <string name="btnSub">subtract</string>
    <string name="btnBack">Back</string>
    <string name="user">username</string>
    <string name="pass">passsword</string>
    <string name="show">show password</string>
    <string name="toast">Toast</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="number">Enter number</string>
    <string name="btnincre">Increment</string>
    <string name="btndecre">Decrement</string>
    <string name="text">Text</string>
    <string name="display">Display</string>
    <string name="title_activity_logins">Logins</string>
    <string name="title_activity_geeks">Geeks</string>
    <string name="title_activity_counters">Counters</string>
    <string name="title_activity_add_sub">Add_sub</string>
    <string name="title_activity_tabs">TabsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">AboutActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">HomeActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_contact">ContactActivity</string>
    <string name="story">        I also have a solid ethic background with a professional
commitment and responsibility as well as an excellent attitude 
to deal with people, a high ommunicative outlook and enhanced 
leadership skills, adaptability to changing situations. 
I am good at working in a team, persistent 
and aimed to get the best results. I am a confident, 
highly driven graduate with practical hands-on customer 
service and travel experience. Resourceful and proactive, 
I combine effective communication skills with detailed 
product knowledge to identify commercial opportunities 
and deliver a satisfactory outcome for both customer and 
company whilst working alone and as part of a larger team. 
I am currently looking for an opportunity to further
 my career within the travel and tourism industry.</string>
    <string name="head">contact form</string>
    <string name="name">Name</string>
    <string name="add">Address</string>
    <string name="sub">subject</string>
    <string name="mess">messsage</string>
    <string name="btnsub">submit</string>
    <string name="btncan">Cancel</string>
    <string name="histo">     I am a Professional with a high creative capability based
      on a scientific, technological and researcher background 
      which allow me to plan, design,built, control, pinpoint, 
      manage, assess, standardize and advice at everything about
       electrical system field specifically on generation, 
       transportation, distribution, wirings and electrical 
       signal analysis attempting to use these resources in 
       a efficiently way,Currently living in Australia .
        I also have a solid ethic background with a professional
         commitment and responsibility as well as an excellent
          attitude to deal with people, a high ommunicative outlook
           and enhanced leadership skills, adaptability to changing 
           situations. I’m good at working in a team, persistent
            and aimed to get the best results. I am a confident, 
            highly driven graduate with practical hands-on customer 
            service and travel experience. Resourceful and proactive, 
            I combine effective communication skills with detailed
             product knowledge to identify commercial opportunities 
             and deliver a satisfactory outcome for both customer 
             and company whilst working alone and as part of a larger team.
             I also have a solid ethic background with a professional commitment
              and responsibility as well as an excellent attitude to deal with
               people, a high ommunicative outlook and enhanced leadership skills, 
               adaptability to changing situations. I’m good at working in a team, 
               persistent and aimed to get the best results. I am a confident, highly 
               driven graduate with practical hands-on customer service and travel experience. 
               Resourceful and proactive, I combine effective communication skills with detailed 
               product knowledge to identify commercial opportunities and deliver a satisfactory 
               outcome for both customer and company whilst working alone and as part of a larger 
               team. I am currently looking for an opportunity to further my career within the 
               travel and tourism industry.</string>
    <string name="topic">About Us</string>
    <string name="soci">follow us on:</string>
    <string name="aki">     Education is one of the most important areas for Kenya with of 
     GDP and some  of Govt expenditure committed to the sector.
      By providing a platform where children can think and explore new ideas 
      away from the school curriculum, besides it will also help them review 
      and add on what they have been learning in the hacker camps this being the 
      case the children will be more interested in such events and will always look 
      forward for the next.
      Through the application the parents can be able to tell how well their children
       understand things. Entrepreneurship is creativity, from here children 
       ability to solve problems and their approach towards the same can be noted this 
       being the case parents will be able to know about the personality of their own 
       children which in return will enhance good relationship between the two parties 
       since they will be able to understand each other well.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">SplashScreen</string>
    
    
    
    
    
    <string name="username">Akirachix</string>
    <string name="phoneNumber">0713424556</string>

</resources>
